The page builder platform.
Okay.
This was , a request from a solar panel
company that operates worldwide, operates
a lot in the United States, a lot in
the EMEA region, and a lot in APAC.
So they had this need of
offering to their installers.
The installers are third part companies
that sometimes they can be very
small, just one person operation.
Some installer companies are a little
bit bigger, but the installers buy solar
panels from this big solar company.
So they wanted to give to these installers
a marketing tool, a powerful marketing
tool so they can have a website, because
a lot of them didn't have a website.
Can you imagine?
So they wanted these installers to
have, a powerful, modern looking,
very nice, responsible everything.
And then we built the platform.
Yeah, we managed to talk with some of
the installers and talked with some
high hierarchy people in the solar.
Company and then we built
the whole ecosystem.
The ecosystem itself, it's not so complex.
I built two web applications.
One is the editor that they can actually
sso into this web application from
another app that we also implemented.
They can SSO into, they can choose.
Whatever components they
want to have on the page.
Some components are specific to
the installers, so they can, for
instance, they can have their own
text so they can add photos of the
installations that they have done.
So on one side, on part is that, and
some of the components are marketing.
From the solar panel company.
So it was a very win-win for them
because when the final customers entered
the installer company website that
they have created, they would see the
information about that specific installer.
But they would be seeing a lot of content
from the solar panel company about
their products, about how they operate.
It was really the strategy.
Over that.
So the system itself, okay, it
has these two web applications.
There is one rest, API built in node
in the middle that perform all the CRUD
operations that we need in this system.
It connects to a cloud sql.
There is in this diagram, and we have
some data streams that send the data to.
Big query for, just for reports
on Looker Studio and the reports.
We can tell how many pages we have created
the last month , which country has.
Our pages created over time.
So we have basically, the whole
data into the BigQuery and then
the report team can build whatever
they want with this information.
And of course, without sensitive
information of course, but
the statistics and everything
are streamed to this BigQuery.